Guide to Papers of the Kellogg Family 1749-1945 MS 341
New-York Historical Society
Kellogg Family Papers
1749-1945
New-York Historical Society
Kellogg family
MS 341
16 Linear feet (31 boxes)
Correspondence, bills and receipts, genealogical material, photographs, clippings, notebooks, diaries, deeds, wills, inventories, and miscellaneous items, 1749-1945, of various members of the Kellogg and related Baker, Comstock, Snow, and White families of Brooklyn, Port Kent, and Onondaga County, New York; particularly Charles White Kellogg (1815-1896); Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg (1821-1900); and their children Peter Comstock Kellogg (1841-1905) of Montclair, New Jersey; Gertrude Kellogg (1843-1903), a prominent New York actress; and Fanny Kellogg (1848-1948).
Provenance
Donation of Mrs. F. Leighton Meserve, 1985.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to twenty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.) See guidelines in Reading Room for details.
Biographical Note
The Kellogg Family was active in Brooklyn, Port Kent, and Onondaga County, New York; Montclair, New Jersey; and elsewhere.
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, papers, genealogies, bills and receipts, newspaper clippings, financial records, photographs, diaries, deeds, wills, inventories, and printed material, 1749-1945 of various members of the Kellogg and related Baker, Comstock, Snow and White Families of Brooklyn, Port Kent, and Onondaga County, New York and Montclair, New Jersey; particularly Charles Kellogg White (1815-1896); Demnis Dewey Comstock Kellogg (1821-1900); and their children Peter Comstock Kellogg (1841-1945) of Montclair, New Jersey; Gertrude Kellogg (1843-1903), a prominent New York actress; and Fanny Kellogg (1843-1943). The collection largely consists of correspondence between these family members and letters from other members received by Fanny Kellogg. The correspondence primarily concerns family matters, daily life in Brooklyn, and visits to Port Kent, New York.
Other subjects include the career and travels of Gertrude Kellogg, most specifically her performances in Canada, 1874-1875, and in England, 1880-1883, and her work with the Booth-Barrett Company in the mid-western United States; the Kellogg property at Port Kent; Peter C. Kellogg and Company, a thorough-bred horse and livestock firm; the real estate activities of Isaac V. Baker in Washington County, New York and his association with the Bethlehem Iron Company; and the Kellogg's interest in spiritualism. Also included in the collection are letters from various spiritualists and clairvoyants, 1857-1910, often accompanied by patented recipes for medicines; records kept by Fanny Kellogg of her Red Cross Sewing School classes in Plattsburg, New York, 1919-1925, and at Port Kent, 1898 and 1922; diaries kept by Charles White Kellogg while living in New York City, 1851-1852 (2 vols.), which concern his affairs as a produce commission merchant and his interest in spiritualism; a diary kept by Julia Burwell Snow (1842-1892), in Buffalo, New York, 1859 (1 vol.); plays and reading material of Gertrude Kellogg; and photographs of most members of the Kellogg family.
Arrangement
The papers are organized by family member and by type of material.
Actresses.; Acting.; Diaries.; Wills.; Inventories; Genealogies (histories); Onondaga County (N.Y.).; Deeds.; Brooklyn (N.Y.); Port Kent (N.Y.); Spiritualism; Livestock; American Red Cross; Baker (Family); Baker, Isaac V., 1813-1894; Bethlehem Iron Company; Booth, Edwin, 1833-1893; Kellogg, Charles White, 1815-1896; Kellogg, Demmis Dewey Comstock, 1821-1900; Kellogg, Fanny, 1848-1948; Kellogg, Gertrude, 1843-1903; Kellogg, Julia Burwell Snow, 1842-1892; Kellog, Peter Comstock, 1841-1905; Peter C. Kellogg and Company; Snow family; St. John, Silas; White family
- Box 1: Charles White Kellogg- Correspondence and Papers
  - Charles White Kellogg to Laura Baker, 1875 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Charles White Kellogg to Harvey S. Bowen, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Charles White Kellogg to Alvan Kellogg, 1835-1848 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Charles White Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1851-1896 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Charles White Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, undated, 1863-1886 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Charles White Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1872-1888 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Charles White Kellogg to Peter Comstock Kellogg, 1878, 1884 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, undated, 1834-1896 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Record of Spiritual Communication., undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Lawsuit, Kellogg vs Buckley, 1862-1863 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Financial Accounts, 1833-1849 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Financial Accounts, 1868-1893 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Rees Run Petroleum and Mining Co., 1864-1865 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Miscellaneous Business Papers, 1835-1874 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Box 2: Charles White Kellogg- Correspondence, Papers, and Diaries
  - Charles White Kellogg: Estate Papers, 1896-1900 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Death of Charles White Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, Notice of Death, 1896 July (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Death of Charles White Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1896 July (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Death of Charles White Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1896 July (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Death of Charles White Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1896 July (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Death of Charles White Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1896 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Death of Charles White Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy., 1896 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Diary, 1851 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Charles White Kellogg: Diary, 1852 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Box 3: Demmis D. C. Kellogg- Correspondence
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, undated, 1869-1871 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1874-1878 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1886, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1883-1887 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, undated, 1888-1899 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg to Peter Comstock Kellogg, 1892, 1897 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1835, 1869-1899 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Box 4: Demmis D. C. Kellogg- Correspondence and Papers
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Burland Property at Port Kent, 1896-1897 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Christmas Lists, 1889-1899 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Will and Estate Papers, 1896-1902 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Death of Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1900 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Death of Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1900 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Death of Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1900 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Death of Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1900 Feb. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box 5: Fanny Kellogg- Correspondence, Letters to Demmis Kellogg
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1870-1879 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1880-1883 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1890-1892 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Box 6: Fanny Kellogg- Correspondence, Letters to Gertrude Kellogg
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1867-1878 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1879-1880 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1881 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1882 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1883 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1884 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1885 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Box 7: Fanny Kellogg- Correspondence
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1886-1887 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1892-1896 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Charles White Kellogg, 1875-1892 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Fanny Kellogg to Laura Demis Clark Baker, undated, 1905 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Leonora Boughton to Fanny Kellogg, 1869-1876 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Thornton W. Burgess to Fanny Kellogg, 1938-1944 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - F. A. Lane to Fanny Kellogg, 1901 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Minnie Marshall to Fanny Kellogg, 1869-1886 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - William H. Marshall to Fanny Kellogg, 1875-1876 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gabrielle W. Murdock to Fanny Kellogg, 1917-1922 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Silas St. John to Fanny Kellogg, 1912-1916 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mark Sullivan - Fanny Kellogg, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mary Clarke Thompson to Fanny Kellogg, undated, 1870-1876 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Albon V. Tourgee to Fanny Kellogg, 1893-1899 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - A. G. Wells to Fanny Kellogg, 1902-1917 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Wendell L. Willkie - Fanny Kellogg, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Box 8: Fanny Kellogg- Correspondence and Papers
  - Fanny Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1869-1899 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Fanny Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1900-1919 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Fanny Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, undated, 1920-1945 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Fanny Kellogg: "Our Block", "Brooklyn Eagle" Article, 1913, 1915, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Fanny Kellogg: Red Cross Sewing Classes, Port Kent, N.Y. and Plattsburg, N.Y., 1898, 1919-1925 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Fanny Kellogg: Miscellaneous Papers, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Fanny Kellogg: Recipe Book, 1889 (Box 8, Folder unknown container)
  - Fanny Kellogg: Address Book, undated (Box 8, Folder unknown container)
  - Fanny Kellogg: "Record" - Book of Poetry, [1889] (Box 8, Folder unknown container)
- Box 9: Gertrude Kellogg- Correspondence
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Charles White Kellogg, 1871-1882 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1872-1876 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1881-1892 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1880-1895 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Laura Daily Comstock Baker, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Peter Comstock Kellogg, 1872, 1875 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gertrude Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1869-1877 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Julia Donoughue and Mary Walsh to Gertrude Kellogg, 1896 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1869-1886 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, undated, 1887-1903 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Will and Estate Papers, 1899-1905 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Box 10: Gertrude Kellogg- Readings and Scripts
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Readings, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "Elizabeth", undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "Elizabeth", undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "Gyda", undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "Gyda", undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "La Verduga", undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "La Verduga", undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Script of "La Verduga", undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: "Marcellina in Monaldi", undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Scenery Sketches, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Box 11: Gertrude Kellogg- Notices, Programs, and Reviews
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Notices and Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Notices and Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Notices and Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Notices and Reviews, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Programs, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Scenery Sketches, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Actors Fund of America to Gertrude Kellogg: Certificate of Membership, 1889 (Box 11, Folder unknown container)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Commonplace Book, "Books read by G. K.", undated (Box 11, Folder unknown container)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: Commonplace Book, 1894 (Box 11, Folder unknown container)
  - Gertrude Kellogg: "The Daily Journal for 1859, G. Kellogg" (Box 11, Folder unknown container)
- Box 12: Peter Comstock Kellogg- Correspondence
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Charles White Kellogg, 1864-1896 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1860-1892 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1896 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1897 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1898 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1869-1905 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1867-1901 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Box 13: Peter Comstock Kellogg- Correspondence and Papers
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Fanny and Gertrude Kellogg, 1870-1901 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg to Isaac V. Baker (1872), Laura Baker (1869), and Mary E. Comstock (1886), 1869, 1872, 1886, 1869-1886 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - George Sheer Jr. - Peter Comstock Kellogg, 1875-1877 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg: Miscellaneous Business Material, [1879-1895] (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg: Miscellaneous Business Material, [1879-1905] (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Death of Peter Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1905 July (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Death of Peter Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1905 July (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Death of Peter Comstock Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1905 Aug. -1905 Sept. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Peter Comstock Kellogg: New-York Free Academy, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Box 14: Julia Snow Kellogg- Correspondence, Papers and Diary; Charles Snow Kellogg- Correspondence
  - Julia Snow Kellogg to Charles White Kellogg, undated, 1872-1888 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1868-1876 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, undated, 1880-1892 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1869-1876 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1868-1892 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg to Laura Daily Comstock Baker, 1875 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Death of Julia Snow Kellogg: Letters of Sympathy, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg: Diary, Notebook, 1859 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Charles Snow Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, 1880-1892 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Charles Snow Kellogg:"Scrap Book" of Children's Postcards Cut-outs, undated (Box 14)
  - Julia Snow Kellogg: Scrap Book of Newspaper Clippings / Commonplace Book, undated (Box 14, Folder unknown container)
- Box 15: Charles Snow Kellogg- Correspondence and Papers; Evaline A. C. White- Correspondence
  - Charles Snow Kellogg to Demmis Dewey Comstock Kellogg, undated, 1898-1899 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Charles Snow Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1875-1932 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Charles Snow Kellogg to Gertrude Kellogg, 1880, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Charles Snow Kellogg: Will and Estate Papers, 1935-1938 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Charles Snow Kellogg: Marriage Announcement, 1899 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Evaline Augusta Comstock White, 1870-1881 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Evaline Augusta Comstock White, 1882 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Evaline Augusta Comstock White, 1882 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Evaline Augusta Comstock White, 1883-1887 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Evaline Augusta Comstock White, 1892-1897 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Box 16: Comstock Family- Correspondence; Somers Family- Correspondence
  - Comstock, Katharine B., 1869-1886 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Comstock, Katharine B., 1887-1899 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Comstock, Lucy Campbell Jackson, 1805-1806, 1864, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Comstock, Mary E., 1871-1924, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Comstock, Peter, 1833-1874 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Comstock, Peter, Jr., 1870-1875, 1910 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Somers, Anne J.D., 1895-1920, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Somers, Janie, 1915-1918 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Somers, Janet, 1887-1899 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Somers, Margaret (Maggie) Bell, 1920-1922 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Somers, Robert, 1874-1887 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Somers Family, 1880-1896, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Box 17: Ida M. F. Kellogg- Correspondence; Meserve Family- Correspondence
  - Kellogg, Ida May Freeman to Fanny Kellogg, 1899-1937 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Kellogg, Ida May Freeman: Letters Received from Freeman Family and Conde Family, 1892, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Kellogg, Ida May Freeman: Miscellaneous Letters and Papers, 1897-1935, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1912-1919 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1920-1923 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1925-1928 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg to Fanny Kellogg, 1930-1944 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg to Ida M. Freeman Kellogg, 1920-1935, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg: Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1915-1926 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Meserve, Kathleen Kellogg: Miscellaneous Papers, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Meserve Family, 1935-1947 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Box 18: Related Family Members A-F, Correspondence
  - Abbott, Julia Baker, 1886, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Sabrina, 1816 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Baker, Charles Kellogg, 1869-1900 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Baker, George Comstock, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Baker, Helen, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Isaac V.: Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Baker, Isaac V.: Bethlehem Iron Company, 1858-1876 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Baker, Isaac V.: Johnson Ore Beds, 1853-1890 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Baker, Kathleen L., 1869-1876 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Baker, Laura Daily Comstock, 1870-1877 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Baker, Laura Demis Clark, 1874-1922 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Baker, Laurance Clark, 1938-1941 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Baker, Mary, 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Baker, Minnie E. Davis, 1886 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Baker, Sarah A., 1876 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Belden, Hattie E., 1897-1902 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Brewster, Catharine, 1835-1840, undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Campbell, Joshua, 1797 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Carter, Lucy, 1878-1882 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Culver, Lucy Comstock Baker, 1869-1893 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Culver, George B., 1879 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Dewey Family, 1839, 1894 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Dunlop, Laura Comstock White, 1869-1938 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Box 19: Related Family Members G-W; Correspondence
  - Gore Family, 1882 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Harrigan, Harold W., 1918 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Harrigan, Marietta (Minnie) Lucy White, 1871-1897 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Harrigan Family, 1882, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Healy, George, 1835-1836 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Heiser, Leonard K., 1918 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Jackson Family, 1791-1810 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Kellogg, Alvan, 1838 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Kellogg, Day Otis, 1832-1842 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Kellogg, Frederick Snow, 1890-1899 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Kellogg, Israel Phelps, 1877-1882 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - John P. Kellogg and Company, 1859-1866 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Perine Family, 1836-1882 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Snow, Rueben Griswold, 1869 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Snow, George and Marie, 1896-1923 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - White Family, 1749-1863 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Phelps, Annie B., 1874-1875 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Richards Family and Snyder Family, 1880 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Spear, Laura (Ollie) D. Comstock and Nathan, 1877-1906 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Wood, Fleda Perine, 1875-1876 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Box 20: Medical Clairvoyents and Spiritualists, A-Z, Correspondence; Misc. Correspondents, A-F, Correspondence
  - Adams, Evangeline S., 1917 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Campbell, Lily, 1889 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Danskin, Sarah A., undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mettler, J. R. and Samantha, 1857-1896 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Mosley, J. H., 1880 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Newton, J. R., 1869-1883 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Perkins, Isaac C., 1883-1886 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Salisbury, J. H., 1872-1885 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Sizer, Nelson, 1865-1866, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Stephens, Mary J., 1906-1911 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Stephenson, Matthew, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Thrall, Flavia A., 1889-1890 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Walling, M. L., 1907 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - White, F. Gordon, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Medical Clairvoyants and Spiritualists: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Belloc, Hilaire and Elodie, 1896-1914 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Dague Family, 1890-1946 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Fairbanks, Mary M., 1866-1867 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Folan, John, 1900-1917 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Box 21: Misc. Correspondents, G-V: Correspondence; Britton, Campbell, White, Comstock, Jackson Families: Genealogical Material
  - Hogarth, Georgina, 1886-1905 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Neuman, Louise M., 1869-1876 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ransome, George D. C., 1862-1882 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Stephens, Lillian, 1874-1886, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Turk, J. C., 1887, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Upham Family, 1876, 1915 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Yates, Frank, 1862-1913 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Genealogical Material: Britton, Campbell, White Families, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Genealogical Material: Britton, Campbell, White Families, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Genealogical Material: Comstock, Jackson Families, undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Box 22: Comstock, Jackson, Freeman, Kellogg, Snow and Other Families: Genealogical Material
  - Genealogical Material: Comstock, Jackson Families, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Genealogical Material: Kellogg, Freeman Families, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Genealogical Material: Snow Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Genealogical Material: Kellogg, Freeman Families, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Genealogical Material: Babcock Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Genealogical Material: Brewster Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Genealogical Material: Burwell Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Genealogical Material: Griswold Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Genealogical Material: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Genealogical Material: Phelps Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Genealogical Material: Stebbins Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Genealogical Material: Turner Family, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Box 23: Kellogg Family- Legal and Business Papers
  - Stock Transactions, 1897-1936 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Property, 1826-1940 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Inventories, 1840-1906 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1836-1866 (Box 23, Folder 5)